come to the getting started with Oracle
开始使用Oracle
JDBC and Oracle database in this video
本视频中的JDBC和Oracle数据库
we will show you how to quickly set up
我们将向您展示如何快速设置
your Java program to connect to the
您的Java程序以连接到
Oracle database on cloud or on-premise
云或本地上的Oracle数据库
using the latest Oracle JDBC driver
使用最新的Oracle JDBC驱动程序
first the prerequisites you should have
首先，您应该具备的先决条件
provisioned an Oracle database cloud
预配了Oracle数据库云
service or have an Oracle database
服务或拥有Oracle数据库
installed second step is to make sure
安装第二步是要确保
that you have JDK nine or JDK 8 running
您正在运行JDK 9或JDK 8
on your machine third step is to
在您的计算机上的第三步是
download the Oracle JDBC teen driver or
下载Oracle JDBC青少年驱动程序或
JDBC 8hr and the universal connection
JDBC 8hr和通用连接
pool you see Peter chart from OTN after
池之后，您会从OTN看到Peter图表
the prerequisites get the sample code
先决条件获取示例代码
you CP sampled arjavam from github if
您CP从github采样了arjavam
you want to use only the JDBC driver you
您只想使用JDBC驱动程序
can use data source sample dot Java once
一次可以使用数据源示例点Java
you have the sample code update the
您有示例代码更新了
database credentials to point to the
数据库凭证指向
Oracle database that you have access to
您有权访问的Oracle数据库
make sure to update the database URL
确保更新数据库URL
with the hostname port number and the
带有主机名端口号和
service name of your database provide
您的数据库服务名称提供
the required database user and password
所需的数据库用户和密码
the last step is to compile and run the
最后一步是编译并运行
Java program let's begin with opening
让我们从开放Java程序开始
the browser and going to Oracle comm
浏览器并转到Oracle comm
slash JDBC this is the JDBC landing page
斜杠JDBC，这是JDBC登陆页面
we want you to bookmark this page
我们希望您将此页面添加为书签
because this is a great place for the
因为这是一个很棒的地方
latest news downloads and white papers
最新新闻下载和白皮书
and presentations and many more about
和演示文稿以及更多有关
the Oracle JDBC driver once you are here
您来到这里后，即可使用Oracle JDBC驱动程序
click on the Downloads tab and download
单击下载选项卡并下载
the latest JDBC driver the latest JDBC
最新的JDBC驱动程序最新的JDBC
driver is called 201 accept the license
司机叫201接受驾照
agreement and download a JDBC 8hr and
协议并下载JDBC 8hr和
you see Peter jar we recommend you to
您会看到Peter jar，我们建议您
download you see Peter jar which is the
下载，您会看到Peter jar
universal connection polls that hubs
通用连接轮询集线器
achieve performance scalability and high
实现性能可扩展性和高
availability for Java applications next
Java应用程序的可用性
go to github.com
转到github.com
/ Oracle / Oracle TV examples navigate
/ Oracle / Oracle TV示例导航
to Java JDBC connection samples and UCP
Java JDBC连接示例和UCP
sample java once you download this UCP
下载此UCP后，示例Java
sample java update the Sam the URL with
示例Java使用以下命令更新Sam的URL
the hostname port number and the service
主机名端口号和服务
name to point to the database that you
指向您所指向的数据库的名称
have access to also update the username
有权更新用户名
and password in this sample we will get
和此示例中的密码，我们将获得
a connection to the database and we will
与数据库的连接，我们将
perform some database operations after
之后执行一些数据库操作
getting a connection to the database we
与数据库建立连接
are going to create a table and we will
将要创建一个表，我们将
insert two records into the table and we
在表中插入两个记录，我们
will also update a record now create a
还将更新记录，现在创建一个
new directory getting started and copy
新目录开始并复制
UCP sample java on to this folder also
UCP示例Java也在此文件夹上
copy ot TBC 8hr and you see peter char
复制TBC 8hr，您会看到peter char
on to the Lib directory now compile the
现在到Lib目录中编译
UCP sample dot java and run UCP sample
UCP示例点Java并运行UCP示例
you can see that we have successfully
您可以看到我们已经成功
established a connection to the database
建立与数据库的连接
and also perform some database
并执行一些数据库
operations thank you for watching the
行动感谢您的观看
video
视频